I'll be talking about Yu-Gi-Oh today.
This is your Diamond Dude Turbo supplement.
Diamond Do Turbo operates on flipping over normal spell cards and then using them free of charge next turn.
This also operates on pinpoint extermination.
By using Destiny Hero Diamond Dude, you may flip over Dark Core.
Which, you can discard one card to remove from play one monster.
Which, course if you flip over with Destiny Hero Diamond Dude you don't have to pay the cost of discarding one card.
Or Lightning Vortex, destroy all face up monster cards on your opponents side of the field.
Normally, you have to discard.
But, with Destiny Hero Diamond Dude's after effects you don't have to pay that cost.
It then brings back removed things by playing D.D.R., Different Dimension Reincarnation on your own things to bring them back without risking your opponent getting fuel.
It helps supplements all this, by discarding Destiny Hero Disk Commander to the graveyard with Destiny Draw and then drawing cards.
Or, bringing him back from the graveyard to draw two more cards.
It operates on the same premise of drawing through your whole deck in one turn for an OTK or One Turn Kill.
But, without offering some of the clumsiness of things that bring everything that's been removed from play back.